Finding Aid for Engineering Communications & Marketing (University of Michigan) records 1860-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan 1998
- Coded Files
  - Various Photographs and Slides (purple dot), 1860-1993
    - General
      - Wind Tunnels
        - Hypernomic, undated (Box 10)
        - Low Speed, undated (Box 10)
      - Women
        - Electrical Engineering (Box 10)
        - Nuclear (Box 10)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
    - Fundraising Campaign Slides
      - Graduation, 1974 (Box 10)
      - Slide Presentation, 1974 (Box 10)
      - Laboratories and Facilities, 1974 (Box 10)
      - Building Interiors, 1974 (Box 10)
      - North Campus Buildings, 1980-1990 (Box 10)
    - Individuals
      - Dean Anderson, 1937-1940 (Box 10)
      - Robert Archer, undated (Box 10)
      - Arnold Blake, 1968 (Box 10)
      - Badger, undated (Box 10)
      - Bailey, undated (Box 10)
      - Charles F. Brush, undated (Box 10)
      - Campbell, undated (Box 10)
      - Carhart, undated (Box 10)
      - Carpenter, undated (Box 10)
      - C.S. Denison, undated (Box 10)
      - Cornelius Donovan, undated (Box 11)
      - Charles Ezra Greene, undated (Box 11)
      - Arthur Hill, undated (Box 11)
      - Haig Iskenderian, 1941 (Box 11)
      - Clarence "Kelly" Johnson, undated (Box 11)
      - G. Lawton Johnson (class of 1931), undated (Box 11)
      - David Kelso, 1968 (Box 11)
      - William Lear, undated (Box 11)
      - Lovell, undated (Box 11)
      - Bob Martin and Arthur Miller, undated (Box 11)
      - NASA Researchers (Eby, Wessells, Goldberg) (Box 11)
      - Patterson, undated (Box 11)
      - Waldenmyer, undated (Box 11)
      - White, undated (Box 11)
      - Leonard Williams, undated (Box 11)
      - R.C. Wilson, 1968 (Box 11)
      - A. Winchell, circa 1860 (Box 11)
      - George Wisner (Class of 1865), undated (Box 11)
      - DeVolson Wood, undated (Box 11)
      - Robert Woodward (Class of 1872), undated (Box 11)
      - Zimmie, undated (Box 11)
    - Historical Group Photographs
      - Faculty, 1914 (Box 11)
      - Engineering Administration (Dean Atwood Group), 1961 (Box 11)
      - Engineering Council, undated (Box 11)
      - Engineering Research Council, undated (Box 11)
      - Group Photographs, undated (Box 11)
    - Class Photographs
      - Class of, 1865 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1868 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1872 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1883 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1900 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1904 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1905 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1906 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1907 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1908 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1909 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1910 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1911 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1912 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1913 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1914 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1915 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1916 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1917 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1918 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1921 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1922 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1924 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1932 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1934 (Box 11)
      - Class of, 1936 (Box 11)
  - Various Brochures and Programs (Green Dot) (Box 14)
    - Career Leaflets, 1992-1993 (Box 14)
    - All-Alumni Weekend Brochure, 1995 (Box 14)
    - Carmel, 7/28/1992 (Box 14)
    - CAEN Brochure, 4/1/1989 (Box 14)
    - General Photos (Box 14)
    - General Photos (Box 14)
    - Graduate Program (Box 14)
    - MEPO Book, 1987 (Box 14)
    - North Campus Walking Tour (Box 14)
    - Nuclear Engineering Graduate Brochure (Box 14)
    - Research at CoE (Box 14)
    - SPRL Brochure (Box 14)
    - Staff Awards Program, 1992 (Box 14)
    - Society of Women Engineers (Box 14)
    - Tech Day Brochure (Box 14)
    - Wu Program Photos, 1992 (Box 14)
- Visual Materials
  The Visual Material series (1855-2010, bulk 1980-2000, 15.5 linear feet) consists of photographs, slides, and negatives documenting the history and activities of the College of Engineering. This material complements and extends the visual material contained in the earlier coded files series. The Visual Material was received in two separate transfers. The first installment of material designated by the unit as Visual Material was received between1995 and 1998 and comprises the contents of boxes 5-9. An additional 11 feet designated Visual Material by the unit was received in 2010 and comprises the contents of boxes 12-22.
  The Visual Material series is divided into three subseries based upon the Office of Communications & Marketing organization of the records: "Photo Archives," "Slides," and "Photographs, Contact Sheets and Negatives." The "Photo Archives" subseries (1983-1987, 1.5 linear feet) contains a variety of numbered photographs and contact sheets, including photographs of College of Engineering facilities, faculty, students, special projects, and events. The index provides the appropriate labels for each number; however, the numbers are not always consecutive. "Slides" (ca. 1982-1989, 0.7 linear feet) depict College of Engineering facilities and special programs and projects. Some of the slides are labeled either on the slide or on the plastic sleeves housing the slides, but many do not have dates.
  - Photo Archives
    - Index (Box 5)
    - 810412-840507 (Box 5)
    - 840508-840540 (Box 5)
    - 840541-840610 (Box 5)
    - 840701-850125 (Box 5)
    - 850206-850328 (Box 6)
    - 850410-851216 (Box 6)
  - Slides
    - "Miscellaneous Campus and Laboratory Scenes Mostly from North Campus" (Box 6)
    - Aerospace Engineering (AERO) (5 pages) (Box 6)
    - Altens (2 pages), 1982 (Box 6)
    - Dan Atkins: Audrey, Apollo, Epic, CAD Arm, MAC laboratory (5 pages) (Box 6)
    - Karnes CAEN and EPIC (Box 6)
    - Amdahl Computer Slides and CAEN (2 pages) (Box 6)
    - Computer Aided Engineering Network (CAEN) (Box 6)
    - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science, 1984 (Box 6)
    - CAD-CAM Laboratory, 1984 (Box 6)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 6)
      (10 pages)
    - Apollo (7 pages), 1984 (Box 6)
    - Lisa Laboratory (4 pages), 1984 (Box 6)
    - Computer Center (2 pages), 1982 (Box 6)
    - Computer Science and Engineering (Box 6)
    - Electrical and Computer Engineering (Box 6)
    - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (EECS) (11 pages) (Box 6)
    - Nuclear Engineering Students (2 pages) (Box 6)
    - GG Brown (3 pages) (Box 6)
    - Instructional TV Classroom (Box 6)
    - Industrial and Operational Engineering (IOE) (6 pages) (Box 6)
    - Manufacturing Engineering, 1984 (Box 6)
    - Mechanical Engineering and Applied Mechanics (7 pages) (Box 6)
    - Mechanical Engineering: Lisa Lab, Car, GE Robot (3 pages) (Box 6)
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering (NAME) (Box 6)
    - Nuclear Engineering (2 pages) (Box 6)
    - Plasma Bay (7 pages) (Box 6)
    - Nuclear Engineering (Box 6)
    - Robotics in Electrical Engineering (Box 6)
    - Civil Engineering (slide #7-30) (Box 6)
    - Electrical Engineering (slide #1-11) (Box 6)
    - Materials Science and Engineering (slide #1-11) (Box 6)
    - Mechanical Engineering (slide #1-17) (Box 6)
    - Nuclear Engineering (slide #1-6) (Box 6)
    - Industrial Affiliates Program in Robotics (4 pages) (Box 6)
    - General Slides (5 pages) (Box 6)
    - Center for Research on Integrated Manufacturing (CRIM) (Box 7)
    - Solid-State Electronics Lab, 1989 (Box 7)
    - Nuclear Engineering-Hydraulic Arms, 1988 (Box 7)
    - Civil Engineering Class, 1988 (Box 7)
    - College of Engineering and Michigan's Economic Future, Slide Show, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Photographs, Contact Sheets and Negatives
    The "Photographs, Contact Sheets, and Negatives" subseries (1855-2010, 13.6 linear feet) consists of photographs of a wide variety of subjects. The subseries is subdivided into five sub-subseries or sub-categories: "Buildings and Research Facilities," "Events," "Faculty, Staff, Scholars and Donors," "Historical," "Student Life and School Activities," and "Other." The "Buildings and Research Facilities" sub-category (1965-1992, 0.5 linear feet) includes photographs of building construction, completed buildings and laboratories. "Events" (1927-1995, 1.1 linear foot) includes photographs of reunions, commencement, building dedications, conferences, lectures and other events. The Faculty, Staff, Scholars and Donors material (1926-1995, 0.5 linear foot) consists of photographs from staff and faculty gatherings and portraits of scholars, faculty and donors. The "Historical" grouping (1855-2000, 4.5 linear feet) consists of early photographs of the College of Engineering faculty, laboratories, and buildings, including several scrapbooks pertaining to Camp Davis. Other photographs include a series of World War I activities portraying members of the Student Army Training Corps (SATC). The Historical grouping is split into two due to a later addition in 2010 of related material. Those interested in the sub-subseries should check boxes 8-9 as well as boxes 12-14. "Student Life and School Activities" (1967-1997, 0.5 linear feet) contains photographs of student life from the 1960s to the 1990s. The "Other" grouping (1980-2010, 8 linear feet) contains photographs of buildings, people, events, and other college activities that cannot be easily classified under the headings named above.
    - Buildings and Research Facilities
      - Aerospace Building
        - 1983, undated (Box 7)
        - Photographs and Architectural Drawings, 1986 (Folder 1)
      - Applied Mechanics Laboratory, 1982 (Box 7)
      - Francois-Xavier Bagnoud Building
        - Construction, 1991 (Box 7)
        - Architectural Drawings, undated (Box 7)
      - CAEN Lab in Dow Library, 1986 (Box 7)
      - Civil and Environmental Engineering Lab, 1991 (Box 7)
      - Dean's Office, West Engineering Building, 1982 (Box 7)
      - Dow Building Construction, 1981 (Box 7)
      - Dow Laboratories, 1983 (Box 7)
      - Dow Library, 1988 (Box 7)
      - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (EECS), 1986 (Box 7)
      - Engineering Library Interior, undated (Box 7)
      - Freshman Engineering Student Lounge, 1992 (Box 7)
      - G.G. Brown Building Interior, 1983 (Box 7)
      - Hazardous Substance Research Center, undated (Box 7)
      - Industrial and Operations Engineering Building, undated (Box 7)
      - Laitone Courtyard-architectural drawings and negatives, undated (Box 7)
      - Laser Lab, 1986; 1988 (Box 7)
      - Lay Auto Lab, 1986 (Box 7)
      - Lurie Tower-Sketch of Proposal, undated (Folder 1)
      - Michigan Electron Long Beam Accelerator (MELBA), 1988 (Box 7)
      - Michigan Integrated Technology Instruction Center, architectural drawing (Folder 1)
      - Neural Probe Bonding Machine, 1991 (Box 7)
      - North Campus
        - Models and Maps, 1983 (Box 7)
        - Photographs, undated (Folder 1)
      - Phoenix Memorial Laboratory, 1983 (Box 7)
      - Pierpont Commons, 1990 (Box 7)
      - Plasma Laboratory, 1984 (Box 7)
      - Radiation Lab, 1988 (Box 7)
      - Structures Laboratory, 1988 (Box 7)
      - Viscimeter Lab, 1988 (Box 7)
      - Visualization Lab, 1992 (Box 7)
      - West Engineering Building, undated (Box 7)
      - Engineering Laboratories and Research Facilities
        - circa 1965-1970 (Box 7)
        - undated, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Events
      - Alumni Events and Class Reunions
        - All Alumni Weekend, 1987-1989; 3 folders (Box 7)
        - Alumni Events
          - 1958 (Box 7)
          - 1963 (Box 7)
          - 1981 (Box 7)
          - 1981-1986, 5 folders (Box 7)
          - 1991 (Box 7)
          - 1993 (Box 7)
          - 1995 (Box 7)
        - Alumni Society Meeting, 1992; 1994 (Box 7)
        - Class Reunions
          - Class of 1904
            - 1947 (Box 7)
            - 1950, 1961 (Box 7)
          - Class of 1917
            - 1927-1967 (Box 7)
            - 1977 (Box 7)
            - undated (Box 7)
          - Class of 1925, 1975 (Box 7)
          - Class of 1928, 1978 (Box 7)
          - Class of 1932, 1977 (Box 7)
          - Class of 1934, 1984 (Box 7)
          - Class of 1937, 1987 (Box 7)
          - Class of 1945, 1990 (Box 7)
        - Dearborn Area Alumni Dinner, 1991 (Box 7)
        - Navy ROTC Alumni Reunion, 1993 (Box 7)
      - Auto Laboratory Tour, 1992 (Box 7)
      - Bosses Day Belly Dancer, 1980 (Box 7)
      - Campbell Soup Luncheon, 1994 (Box 7)
      - Capital Campaign, 1974-1978; 3 folders (Box 7)
      - Career Day
        - 1968 (Box 7)
        - 1991 (Box 7)
      - Check Presentations and Gift Donations (Box 8)
        - General Motors Presentation of Van, 1968 (Box 8)
        - Squared Presentation, 1981 (Box 8)
        - TRW Check Presentation, 1982 (Box 8)
        - Amoco Foundation Grant Presentation, 1984 (Box 8)
        - Bell Labs Check Presentation, 1984 (Box 8)
        - Chrysler Check Presentation to Society of Women Engineers (SWE) and Society of Minority Engineering Students (SMES), 1986 (Box 8)
        - Chevron Check Presentation to Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering (NAME), 1988 (Box 8)
        - GM Check Presentation to SMES, 1988 (Box 8)
        - Mobile Check Presentation, 1988 (Box 8)
        - TRW Check Presentation, 1988 (Box 8)
        - Unisys Check/Scholarship Presentation, 1988 (Box 8)
        - John Deere Check Presentation, 1991 (Box 8)
        - IBM Fellowship Presentation, 1991 (Box 8)
        - Class of 1939 Check Presentation, 1991 (Box 8)
        - Bendix Check Presentation, undated (Box 8)
      - College Display Modules-International Symposium on Optical Engineering, 1988 (Box 8)
      - Commencement
        - 1984, 3 folders (Box 8)
        - 1985 (Box 8)
        - 1987 (Box 8)
        - 1989 (Box 8)
        - 1990 (Box 8)
        - 1991 (Box 8)
        - undated (Box 8)
      - Conferences
        - Engineering Summer Conference
          - 1967 (Box 8)
          - 1981 (Box 8)
        - UPACAED Conference, 1990 (Box 8)
      - Dedications
        - Solid State Laboratory, Governor James Blanchard, 1987 (Box 8)
        - Optics Laboratory, 1989 (Box 8)
        - Ergonomics Laboratory Dedication, undated (Box 8)
        - Space Research, Senator Donald Riegle, undated (Box 8)
        - Tesla Laboratory, undated (Box 8)
      - EECS Groundbreaking (Box 8)
      - Emeritus Weekend, 1989; 1992 (Box 8)
      - Endowed Professors Dinner, 1992 (Box 8)
      - Engineering Awards Program, 1980 (Box 8)
      - Engineering Fest, 1981 (Box 8)
      - ENIAC Display, 1988 (Box 8)
      - Football Weekends, 1977-1980; 3 folders (Box 8)
      - Honors and Awards Ceremonies
        - Symposium on Solid and Fluid Mechanics, Sesquicentennial Awards Ceremonies, 1968 (Box 8)
        - Whirlpool Foundation Award, Harlan Hatcher, 1968 (Box 8)
        - Honors Brunch, 1993 (Box 8)
        - Honors Luncheon
          - 1974 (Box 8)
          - 1977 (Box 8)
          - 1981 (Box 8)
          - 1983 (Box 8)
        - Industrial Awards Banquet, 1988 (Box 8)
        - Tau Beta Pi Honors Dinner
          - 1982 (Box 8)
        - Society of Women Engineers (SWE) Reception
          - 1987 (Box 8)
          - 1988 (Box 8)
        - PYI Awards Dinner, 1987 (Box 8)
        - Society of Minority Engineering Students (SMES) Awards
          - Banquet, 1991 (Box 8)
          - Dinner, 1988 (Box 8)
          - Luncheon, 1993 (Box 8)
        - High School Scholars Receptions, 1988 (Box 8)
        - Class of 1931 Scholarship Winners, 1990 (Box 8)
      - Ion Beam Lab Dedication, 1986 (Box 8)
      - Lectures
        - ES3 Lecture (Gina Sartor), 1990 (Box 8)
        - Katz Lectures, 1978 (Box 8)
        - Russel Lecture, 1986 (Box 8)
      - MEAM 125th Anniversary Reception, 1993 (Box 8)
      - MEPO, 1988 (Box 8)
      - MJMI, 1993 (Box 8)
      - MLK Event (William Fowble), 1993 (Box 8)
      - NAC Meeting, 1986; 1991 (Box 8)
      - NCR Corporate Visit, 1993 (Box 8)
      - Open House
        - 1957 (Box 8)
        - 1983 (Box 8)
      - President's Club Tour of Dow Building, 1982 (Box 8)
      - Richard Petty Visit, 1989 (Box 8)
      - Senior Reception Davidson Speech, 1988 (Box 8)
      - Schulte Reception, undated (Box 8)
      - Solar Car Presentation, 1992 (Box 8)
      - Summer Science for High School Girls, 1988 (Box 8)
      - Tech Day, 1982; 2 folders (Box 8)
      - Technirama, 1967 (Box 8)
      - Telecast, 1974 (Box 8)
      - UM Research Club and Sigma XI Joint Meeting, 1990 (Box 8)
      - Undergraduate Future Session, 1987 (Box 8)
      - Waldenwood Retreat, 1971 (Box 8)
      - Walking Tours, 1987 (Box 8)
      - Walter Hancock Dinner, 1994 (Box 8)
    - Faculty, Scholars, Staff and Donors
      - Metallurgical Engineering-Staff Picnic, 1926 (Box 8)
      - Electrical Engineering Staff Picnic, 1927 (Box 8)
      - Faculty Portraits, circa 1960 (Box 8)
      - Eveylyn Bruson Retirement Party, 1980 (Box 8)
      - Cartoon Portrait of Engineering Faculty, circa 1980s (Folder 1)
      - Engineering Faculty Awards, 1981 (Box 8)
      - Irene Kendrovich Retirement, 1981 (Box 8)
      - Christmas Party/Barb Whipple Farewell, 1982 (Box 8)
      - Irene Mehler Farewell, 1982 (Box 8)
      - Betty Parkinson Reception, 1982 (Box 8)
      - Stanton Retirement, 1982 (Box 8)
      - Claude Shannon, 1987 (Box 8)
      - Presidential Young Investigators, 1988-1989 (Box 8)
      - Bioengineering Department, 1989 (Box 8)
      - Decatur Rogers, 1989 (Box 8)
      - Minority Engineering Programs Office (MEPO) and Publications Staff, 1990 (Box 8)
      - Robert Lurie and Family, 1990-1997 (Box 8)
      - Alumni Group Fellows, 1992 (Box 8)
      - Placement Office Staff, 1994 (Box 8)
      - Maxine Kumin (Poet-in-Residence), 1996 (Box 8)
    - Historical (1860-2000)
      - Album: "Typical Research Problems ..." of Department of Engineering Research, circa 1928 (Box 8)
      - Composite Portraits Classes of, 1933; 1940 (Folder 1)
      - History of the Mechanical Engineering Laboratory (with photographs of buildings, facilities, and activities), 1937 (Box 8)
      - Early Laboratory view (glass negatives), undated (Box 8)
      - Buildings (Box 8)
      - Camp Davis (Box 9)
        - Class of 1917 at Camp (Box 9)
        - Miscellaneous Views (Box 9)
        - Scrapbook of J.M. Reid, 1916 (Box 9)
        - Scrapbook of Student, Class of 1917 of Activities at Camp Davis, Fort Riley, Camp Funston (Volume 1)
      - Class of Group Photograph, 1915 (Folder 1)
      - Cooley Bridge Dedication, 1935 (Box 9)
      - Faculty and Other Personages (Box 9)
      - Laboratories, Equipment, etc. (Box 9)
      - Miscellaneous and Unidentified (Box 9)
      - Quarterdeck (Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering), 1914-1942 (Box 9)
      - Student Activities (Box 9)
      - Students in Laboratories and Workshops (Box 9)
      - World War I activities
        - Building Mess Facility at U-M (Box 9)
        - Training Exercises, Facilities (Box 9)
      - Departments
        - AERO/ 2 Men Assembling Equipment, 7/9/1989 (Box 12)
        - Aeronautics laboratory, older (Box 12)
        - AERO / Apollo 15 crew/ Scott, Worden, Irwin, 1970s (Box 12)
        - AERO / NASA miscellaneous research photos (Box 12)
        - AERO / space station, 7/31/1986 (Box 12)
        - AOSS / Earth/ MI from space, 7/8/1989 (Box 12)
        - AOSS laboratories/miscellaneous, older (Box 12)
        - Applied Mechanics Laboratory, older (Box 12)
        - Auto Lab/ North Campus, 1950s (Box 12)
        - Auto Repair/ Road Work during World War I, late, 1910s (Box 12)
        - Biomed/ Biomechanics Lab, older (Box 12)
        - Bioengineering Research/Miscellaneous, older (Box 12)
        - Camp Davis, 1879; 1885; 1912 (Box 12)
        - Chemical Engineering/Research Equipment, 1968 (Box 12)
        - Dodge Engine/ Placing Pistons, older/1921 (Box 12)
        - EECS, 1980s (Box 12)
        - EECS/ Microwave Anechoic Chamber/ Radiation Lab, older (Box 12)
        - EECS / Molecular Beam Epitaxy, 9/1/1986 (Box 12)
        - Engine Block and Crank Case, older, 1920s (Box 12)
        - ENIAC/Arthur Banks, 1946 (Box 12)
        - Environmental Engineers/Michigan Engineer/Walt Weber, Steven Wright Marilyn Barger, Linda Abriola, Kim Hayes, 5/30/1991 (Box 12)
        - Fairbanks-Morse Oil Engine, January, 1936 (Box 12)
        - Fission Products Lab, older (Box 12)
        - Forge Foundry/ Chem & Metall/ East Eng. Bldg., 1950s (Box 12)
        - Forging Furnace, older (Box 12)
        - Glassblower Peter Severn, Harald Eberhart/MI Engineer, Summer 1991 (Box 12)
        - Machine Shop, 1890 (Box 12)
        - Machine Shop, 1904 (Box 12)
        - Machine Shop, 1917 (Box 12)
        - MEAM Lab/Students, 1995-1996 (Box 12)
        - Multiple Disc Clutch, older, 1917 (Box 12)
        - NAME, Ships, Propellers, and Tow Tank, older (Box 12)
        - NAME, Tow Tank (Box 12)
        - NERS-Ford Nuclear Reactor-Phoenix Memorial Project, 1962 (Box 12)
        - Refrigerating Plant/ 24 Hour Test, 1/17/1913 (Box 12)
        - Rocket Launcher, older (Box 12)
        - Sensory Nerve, 1991 (Box 12)
        - Urban Vehicle, 1972 (Box 12)
        - Wind Tunnel, older (Box 12)
        - WWI Auto Dept., 1917-1918 (Box 12)
        - WWI Machine Shop, 1917-1918 (Box 12)
        - WWI Misc., 1917-1918 (Box 12)
        - WWI Phone Class & Parts, 1917-1918 (Box 12)
        - Close-up of Circuit Board, older (Box 12)
        - Old Equipment-Pipes & Valves, unknown (Box 12)
      - Buildings
        - Ashmun St. Bridge in Sault Ste. Marie, 7/3/1935 (Box 12)
        - Auto Mechanics Building, older (Box 12)
        - Automotive Laboratory, older (Box 12)
        - Cooley Building-Interior Architects Renderings, 1945 (Box 12)
        - Dow Building, older (Box 12)
        - Gas Dynamics-Laboratories/Wind Tunnel, September 1966 (Box 12)
        - G.G. Brown-'36e Lounge (Blue Lounge), June 1988 (Box 12)
        - G. G. Brown Building, older (Box 12)
        - G.G. Brown/ Dow, Architects Drawing (Box 12)
        - Institute of Science and Technology (IST), older (Box 12)
        - EECS Building Construction, 11/1/84, 01/10/1985 (Box 12)
        - EECS Building Dedication (Box 12)
        - Engineering Laboratory/Shops Building/ Mechanical Lab, 1886 (Box 12)
        - Engineering Shops Building, 1904 (Box 12)
        - First Engineering Building, 1881-82 (Box 12)
        - First Library, older (Box 12)
        - Forge Shop/ Interior, 1909 (Box 12)
        - Forge Shop/ Wm. Macdonald, 1904 (Box 12)
        - Historical Interiors, early, 1900s (Box 12)
        - Industrial Technology Institute (ITI) Building, February 1984 (Box 12)
        - Library (Box 12)
        - New Engineering Center Building Sketch, 1984 (Box 12)
        - North Campus, 1923-4 (Box 12)
        - North Campus Aerials, 10/17/1985 (Box 12)
        - North Campus Aerials 80's, 1970s (Box 12)
        - North Campus Aerials, 1960s (Box 12)
        - North Campus Buildings, 1980s (Box 12)
        - North Campus Buildings/Scenes, September 1981 (Box 12)
        - North Campus Diag (Box 12)
        - Phoenix Memorial Laboratory Architect's Drawing, 1950s (Box 12)
        - Alumni Memorial Hall, older (Box 12)
        - Art & Architecture Building, 7/1/1984 (Box 12)
        - Burton Tower, older (Box 12)
        - Central Campus Scenes, 1970s; 1980s (Box 12)
        - East Engineering, 1925-30 (Box 12)
        - Old Physics Laboratory, older (Box 12)
        - Plans/Layout For UM School for Telephone Electricians, 10/10/1918 (Box 12)
        - Research Activities Building, older (Box 12)
        - Roebling's Bridges, older (Box 12)
        - U-M President's House, 1981 (Box 12)
        - U-M President's House, 1897 (Box 12)
        - University of Michigan, 1864 (Box 12)
        - University of Michigan, 1855 (Box 12)
        - West Engineering Arch & Tower/Summer, 1980s (Box 12)
        - West Engineering, 1930 (Box 12)
        - West Engineering, 1938 (Box 12)